database = [
    {
        question: 'Select the most correct word: The students had to give an (oral, aural) presentation for their final.',
        optionA: 'Oral',
        optionB: 'Aural',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'Select the most correct word: The ancient (Oracle, auricle)revealed wise words to live by.',
        optionA: 'Oracle',
        optionB: 'Auricle',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'Select the most correct word: Being an (odd, awed) ball means living out the box.',
        optionA: 'Awed',
        optionB: 'Odd',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'Select the most correct word: As time paced the students had only an (hour, our) left in the exam.',
        optionA: 'Hour',
        optionB: 'Our',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'Select the most correct word: The prisoner awaited in his (sell, cell) before the trial',
        optionA: 'Sell',
        optionB: 'Cell',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'The definition of ‘Abstract’ is:',
        optionA: 'Adjective – theoretical, not applied or practical; not concrete; hard to understand.',
        optionB: 'Noun – an outcast. ',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'The definition of ‘Bizarre’ is:',
        optionA: 'Adjective – strikingly odd in appearance or style; grotesque.',
        optionB: 'Noun – the condition of being doubtful or confused.',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'The definition of ‘Cajole’ is:',
        optionA: 'Adjective - hard to please; dainty in taste',
        optionB: 'Verb - to persuade by pleasant words or false promises',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'The definition of ‘Decadence’ is:',
        optionA: 'Adjective - out of date',
        optionB: 'Noun - decay; decline',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'The definition of ‘Efface’ is:',
        optionA: 'Verb - to wipe out; to erase',
        optionB: 'Verb- to gather and store away; to collect',
        answer: 'A'
    }
]